prevuehr.com 2017-08-28

# Privacy Policy - Prevue HR

**Introduction**  
Prevue HR Systems (“Prevue”) allows this website (the “Site”) to collect personally identifying information about you only when you specifically and knowingly provide it to us.

**Basic Statement**  
Personally identifying information that you provide to the Site will not be made available to third parties outside of the Site without your explicit permission.

The Site collects personally identifying information about you only when you specifically and knowingly provide it to us.

The Site may make aggregate information about our customers (e.g. overall statistics) available to third parties for certain purposes. Information that personally identifies you will be kept strictly confidential.

Personally identifying information which you choose to provide to another party or website will be subject to their privacy policy. For example, if you purchase goods or services online from a merchant you found while using the Site, information you provide to that merchant is subject to their privacy policy rather than ours.

**What Is “Personally Identifying Information”?**  
“Personally identifying information” is information that can be explicitly used to identify and/or contact you as an individual. This includes information like your real name, e-mail address, mailing address, phone number, credit card number, etc. Information that, by itself, cannot be explicitly linked with your “real” identity is not considered personally identifying. Examples of this are favourite or bookmarked Web sites, or your preferences with respect to how you wish to see a given page or site set up according to the selections you choose.

On occasion, the Site may ask you for personal information such as your name or address. We do this when you register for services that require registration or subscription. The Site needs to collect this information for providing assessment services and for tracking/verifying compliance with Site policies. It may also be needed for purposes of compliance with federal, provincial and local laws.

**Use of Cookies**  
Cookies are pieces of information that a Web site transfers to an individual’s hard disk for record-keeping purposes. Cookies can make the Web more useful by storing information about your preferences on a particular site, like what items you have in a “shopping cart” for an online store. The use of cookies is an industry standard, and many major Web sites use them to provide great features for their customers.

The Site has two primary uses for its cookies. First, we use them to specify unique preferences. Secondly, we use cookies to track user trends and patterns. This helps us better understand and improve areas of the Site service that our users find valuable. While both of these activities depend on the use of a “cookie,” visitors to the Site always have the option of disabling cookies via their browser preferences.

Most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies. You can reset your browser to refuse all cookies or indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, note that some parts of the Site service may not function properly if you refuse cookies.  
Links to other Sites  
Users should be aware that when you are on the Site, you could be directed to other sites that are beyond our control. There are links to other sites from the Site pages that take you outside our service. These other sites may send their own cookies to users, collect data or solicit personal information.

Prevue’s policy does not extend to anything that is inherent in the operation of the Internet, and therefore beyond the Site’s control, and is not to be applied in any manner contrary to applicable law or governmental regulation.

**E-mail to Us**  
When you send us e-mail, we will use your name and e-mail address only to respond to the concerns you write to us with. Your e-mail may be shared with appropriate people within the Prevue organization to help us respond to your concerns and improve the Site.

**Changes to this Policy**  
From time to time, Prevue may introduce new products and services to its users and members. Prevue reserves the right to modify this policy at any time by notifying customers, via the Site, of a new privacy policy. You can write to us at support@prevuehr.com with any further questions.
